Guide to the Stanford University, Institute for Diversity in the Arts, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Institute for Diversity in the Arts, records
1982-2008
SC1179
Stanford University. Institute for Diversity in the Arts.
16.5 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical/Historical note
The Institute for Diversity in the Arts (IDA) + Committee on Black Performing Arts (CBPA) is an interdisciplinary program in the humanities that involves students in the study of culture, identity and diversity through artistic expression. Their mission is to create, support, and advance powerful, collaborative, and transformative arts practice and arts leadership.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of audiovisual recordings of IDA, CBPA and other related events.
Access Terms
Art, American--Study and teaching.; Art.; Performing arts--California; Performing arts.; Stanford University--Students.
Collection Contents
- Audiovisual materials, 1982-2008; Accession ARCH-2014-024
  - ArtShow: Youth and Community Development (56:40), Alweis Productions, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Short on Sugar (9:49), Bratty Girl Productions, Undated (Box 1)
  - Allah Tantou: God's Will (62:00), California Newsreel, 1991; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Sango Malo: The Village Teacher, California Newsreel, 1991; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Interstellar Highway, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - In Time (19:00), Backdoor Films, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - "11/24/04 Runthru", 2004; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Loose tape in Maxell videocassette box, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - "Our History 3/27/93 – 4/17 – 4/24", 1993; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - "Umzansi w/ 7th Graders" – East Palo Alto School Workshop, 8 Nov 2001; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Unprecedented: The 2000 Presidential Election (50:00), 2002; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Black Decision Makers #1 of 3, 23 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Black Decision Makers #2 of 3, 23 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Black Decision Makers #3 of 3, 23 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Blacks in Practical Production #1 of 3, 30 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Blacks in Practical Production #2 of 3, 30 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Blacks in Practical Production #3 of 3, 30 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Black Decision Makers / Blacks in Practical Production (1:34), 9 Jun 1993; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Benjamin Franklin Abolitionist: Eighteenth-Century Africans in Motion, Franklin & Marshall U, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - EPA Workshop 1 of 2, 1994 Dec 4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - EPA Workshop 2 of 2, 1994 Dec 4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - "Short Clip of EPA Documentary" ("Clip of Doc."), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - "Clip of Document." ("Clip of Docu."), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - ASD EPA History: #21 Polynesian Outreach #3, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - ASD EPA History: #32 Latino Community Council #1, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - ASD EPA History: #33 Latino Community Council #2 Rubin, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - ASD EPA History: #34 Latino Community Council, Viet. Temple, Coley Grafitti, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - ASD EPA History: #42 Polynesian Outreach #4, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - ASD EPA History: #42 Polynesian Outreach #5, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - ASD EPA History: #44 Chavez Academy Inaguration [sic], 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - "Watch Me Move": Black movement styles in the 20th century, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Black Theatre: Moving Towards the 21st Century, 1989 Jan 22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Black Theatre: Moving Towards the 21st Century Plenary Session, 1989 Jan 24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Black Theatre: Moving Towards the 21st Century: WRAP UP, 1989 Jan 24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Taebo Instructional: The Ultimate Total Body Workout for Men & Women (40:00), Billy Blanks, 1998; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - "Whiskey Gulch Clip", Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Oyamo's Dancing on the Brink Play in Progress, 1995 Feb 28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Silence, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Cured at Nairobi: Messengers 2, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Loose tape in Maxell Black Magnetite Formulation, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Ed Becks at the "EPA Beyond 2000" Community Building Meetings + Interview, 14 Nov 1998; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Cherrie & Oyamo Readings / EPAP Plays in Progress, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - The Committee on Black Performing Arts Presents a Keynote Address By Prof. Margaret B. Wilkerson, 1989; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - CBPA Wilkerson Lecture, 1987; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Robert Moses' Kin, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Nairobi Reunion Tape, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - For Fire Fool A Rough Edit, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - I Am That I Am: Woman, Black (10:01), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Picture Powdermorn Excerpts, Zaccho Dance Theatre, 2000; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Philadanco 1999 Promo, Video D Studios, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - African American Dance Ensemble (6:30), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - African American Dance Ensemble In Concert (Clips (23:00), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Sharing Africa through Dance, Drama, Music, Poetry and the Drum (15:00), Oriki Theater, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Hip Hop Cubano (12:19), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Unspoken, Studio B, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Will Power The Gathering, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Excerpts from Children of the Passage, Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 1999; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - "The Late Show" w/ David Lettermen, Apr 2000; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Aya De Leõn Performing at the Afro Solo Arts Festival (24:00), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Speak Out Presents Aya De León ~ Performance Poet (6:15), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Loose untitled tape, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Kresge Aud Tape 1, 1988 Jan 23; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - "3", Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Spring Migration '90 Dress Rehearsal "Adan/Remembered"/"BodyTalk", 8 May 1990; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Black Performing Arts Wilkerson Lecture Graphics Master, 3 Aug 1989; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Black Performing Arts Dub of Edited Master, 10 Aug 1989; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Black Performing Arts WO 8781 New BU, 22 Jul 1987; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Black Media Workshop Knox 8, 27 Apr 1982; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Katherine Dunham Title Graphics, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Black Decision Makers Edited 3/4" Master, 9 Jun 1993; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Katherine Dunham at Mem Aud (not full copy), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Blacks in Practical Production Edited 3/4" Master, 8 Jun 1993; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Drum Class Ravenswood/EPA, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Final Cut: CBPA Panel with Sandra Faye, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Black Performing Arts Panel #2, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 4)
  - Below the Skin Window, Gina Hernandez's copy, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Art Gallery 3/14/03 (Raw Footage), 14 Mar 2003; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Cherrie and Oyamo Readings: EPAP Plays in Progress, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Cheap but Deep (Final w/ Titles), 14 Apr 2003; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Reel Black Film Festival: Angela Northington/Marcus Shelby, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Dr WEB Du Bois, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Court Martial of Jackie Robinson, 1990; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - World Beat, A. Jacquie Taliaferro, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Colors of Love: Love is a Process: Voices of Colour, John Shasaumi, 14 Feb 2000; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - John O'Neal in You Can't Judge a Book By Looking at the Cover, Western and Southern Arts Associates, Sept 1986; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Baraka Speech, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Anisi Baraka Kresge Auditorium, 18 Oct 2002; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Arts & Minds #87: Baraka, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Darne Towne Follies: Buriel Clay, A. Rhone, June. 1992; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Untold Legacy, Third World Newsreel, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Praise House, Third World Newsreel, 1991; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Natural Man, Fred Luminoso, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Tape #1 Morshell Jones "Black Aesthetic", Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Tape #2 Morshell Jones, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Katherine Dunham and her Contribution to American Dance, 12 May 1989; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Last Black Man Overture & Tape #1, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Last Black Man Tape #2 of 2, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Mabrak Live in Mtn. View, California, Lightning & Thunder Music, 1991; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Dance Black America, PBS, 1985; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Maskarade Act 1, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Maskarade Act 2, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Maskarade Act 3, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Phylise Smith – Classes & Choreography, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Fairwell to Halifu Osumare, 9 Dec 1993; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Joe Turner's Come and Gone, 11 Nov 1994; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - David Alonzo Jones Modern Jazz II Class, 6 Apr 1994; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Performance Arenas in African American History – Beverly Robinson, 5 Dec 1990; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Robert Moses In Progress, 11 Sep 1998; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Colored Museum, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Queenie Pie Harlem Duet / Shaken Mess Out of Misery, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Denise Morris Comm 114 Projects, 1992; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Untitled [water damage], Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Meyer Library Exhibit Opening, 2 Apr 1987; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - The Avant-Garde and the Concept of a Black Aesthetic: Expanding Definitions... Breaking Boundaries, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - O. Butler, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - The Wedding Project Pre-Video, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - The Wedding Project Raw Footage Balcony View, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - The Wedding Project Raw Footage Floor View, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Black Decision Makers #1 of 3, 23 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 6)
  - Black Decision Makers #2 of 3, 23 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 6)
  - Black Decision Makers #3 of 3, 23 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 6)
  - Blacks in Practical Production #1 of 3, 30 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 6)
  - Blacks in Practical Production #2 of 3, 30 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 6)
  - Blacks in Practical Production #3 of 3, 30 Apr 1993; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 6)
  - Margaret Wilkerson Lecturer Edited Master, 9 Aug 1989; 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 6)
  - Unlabelled tapes, 1 videotape(s) (BetaCam SP) (Box 6)
  - Mountain Horse: Unlabelled cassettes, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: New Age Rhythm & Blues, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: […]tation, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: CA Mix/Danish, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: Abba etc, Feb. 2001; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: Hands Up etc, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: Car, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: Delirium, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: Krinmor bara, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: Agnetha Fältskog, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: Flicka / Pojke, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: I believe in you & me 1, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: I believe in you & me 2, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: Oldies, July 2000; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: Beatles 7, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: Mike Oldfield, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: Stille, July 2000; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mountain Horse: Shubidua 1, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - IDA Festival 2003 Footage: Carthographies of Race Reel, 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - IDA Festival 2003 Footage: Cheap But Deep Final Final (DV Cam), 14 Mar 2003; 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - IDA Festival 2003 Footage: Cheap But Deep Final Final (Mini DV), 14 Mar 2003; 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - IDA Festival 2003 Footage: Ollin Wide Tape #1, 11 Mar 2003; 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - IDA Festival 2003 Footage: Ollin Tape 2, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - Ollin, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - IDA Below The Skin dub, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - Art Gallery, Stanford Tape 1 of 2, 14 Mar 2003; 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - Art Gallery, Stanford Tape 2 of 2, 14 Mar 2003; 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - IDA Just/Art Footage: Spoken Word & Music 1, 9 Nov 2002; 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - IDA Just/Art Footage: Spoken Word & Music 2, 9 Nov 2002; 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - IDA Just/Art Footage: Visual Art 1, 9 Nov 2002; 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - IDA Just/Art Footage: Visual Art 2, 9 Nov 2002; 1 videotape(s) (Mini-DV) (Box 7)
  - Dunham, Katherine
    - "A Walk Through Katherine Dunham's Life" May 7, 1989, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Conversations with Katherine Dunham (July 5, 1990), 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Conversations with Katherine Dunham (June 20, 1990), 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Katherine Dunham Lecture – Camera Master – May 9, 1989 Tape #4 Anthro 109, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Katherine Dunham and her Contributions to American Dance – NATIONAL SYMPOSIUM May 12, 1989 (Morning Session), 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Katherine Dunham at the EPA Library 6/13/90, 1990; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Katherine Dunham Lecture – Camera Master – May 2, 1989 Tape #1 Anthro 109, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Katherine Dunham Lecture – Camera Master – May 2, 1989 Tape #2 Anthro 109, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Katherine Dunham Lecture – Camera Master – May 4, 1989 – Tape #3 Anthro 109, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Katherine Dunham Workshop A & B (120:00), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Katherine Dunham Workshop C & D (120:00), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Katherine Dunham Workshop E & F (120:00), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Katherine Dunham Workshop G &H (120:00), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Katherine Dunham Workshop I & J (120:00), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Katherine Dunham Workshop K & L (120:00), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Katherine Dunham Workshop M, N & O (60:00), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Katherine Dunham Workshop P, Q & R (60:00), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Katherine Dunham Workshop S & T (120:00), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Katherine Dunham + Ralph Lemon, 24 Jul 1990; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
    - Conversations with Katherine Dunham, 20 Jun 1990; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
    - Conversations with Katherine Dunham, 5 Jul 1990; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
    - Conversations with Katherine Dunham, 11 Jul 1990; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
    - Katherine Dunham – The Lady and Her Legacy, 14 Apr 1989; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
    - Katherine Dunham Residency: Dunham Video Documentary (3.5" diskette), Undated (Box 7)
    - Katherine Dunham Residency: A Walk Thru Katherine Dunham's Life, 7 May 1989; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
    - Katherine Dunham Residency: Katherine Dunham and Her Contributions to American Dance, 12 May 1989; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
    - Katherine Dunham Residency: Katherine Dunham Lecture Tape #1, 2 May 1989; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
    - Katherine Dunham Residency: Katherine Dunham Lecture Tape #2, 2 May 1989; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
    - Katherine Dunham Residency: Katherine Dunham Lecture Tape #3, 2 May 1989; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
    - Katherine Dunham Residency: Katherine Dunham Lecture Tape #4, 2 May 1989; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Black Theater Conference: Welcome Address, 22 Jan 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Black Theater Conference: Who Are We? I, 23 Jan 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Black Theater Conference: Aesthetics & Audience Development, 23 Jan 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Black Theater Conference: Keynote Address, 23 Jan 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Black Theater Conference: Enhancing the Three A's, 23 Jan 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Black Theater Conference: Bringing In The Bucks, 23 Jan 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Black Theater Conference: Who Are We? II, 23 Jan 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Black Theater Conference: Resource Sharing, 24 Jan 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Black Theater Conference: Plenary Session, 24 Jan 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Black Theater Conference: Plenary Session (Edited Version), 24 Jan 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Oral History Interview: Laverne Spaulding Govorko + Family, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Marva Als, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Familia Jimenez, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Familia Chavez, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Familia Alvarado / Familia Ipiña, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - People on the Street #1, 11 Mar 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Omowale Satterwhite #2, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Albert Galvan – Presentation, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Albert Galvan / Arnold Sanchez, 7 Mar 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Albert Nakai, 9 Mar 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Albert Nakai #2, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Interview of Daniela Gomez and Chavela Rivera, Arviza et al., Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Leroy Musgraves #1/#2, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Leroy Musgraves #2, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Miriam Turner Eads #1, 16 Mar 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Miriam Turner Eads #1, 17 Mar 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Miriam Turner Eads #2 / Barbara Mortion, 8 Mar 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Gertrude Wilks #1, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Gertrude Wilks #2, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Interview: Abraham Tony, 25 Aug 1993; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Mr & Mrs Wilson / Brother Anthony, 4 Mar 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - "Conversations with Katherine Dunham" in Hollywood, 27 Jun 1990; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Black Theater Conference, 24 Jan 1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Avery Brooks, 3 May 1991; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Black Lit Conference / Amiri Baraka, April 1992; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Errol Hill /Sylvia Wynter, 6 Apr 1983; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - "The Arts and the Community", Katherine Dunham, 13 Jun 1990; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Archive of Recorded Sound – The Knoll, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Ntozake Shange 1-3, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Folk Songs, Siparia Welfare Council, 1967; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Ruben Abrica #1, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Ruben Abrica #2, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Interview with Caroll and Emily Damant, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Sandford's Restaurant, 16 Mar 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Trevor Burrowes #2, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Nevida Butler, 10 Mar 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Yen Bui Tran, 14 Mar 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Bob Garcia, 14 Mar 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Bob Hoover #1, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Ed Becks #1, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Ed Becks #2, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Barbara Clarke #1, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Barbara Clarke #2, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Just/Art: Visual Art Session, 9 Nov 2002; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Just/Art: Visual Art/Video Session, 9 Nov 2002; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Just/Art: Music Workshop/Spoken Word, 9 Nov 2002; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Loose, untitled tape, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Gina 4-3657 (3.5" diskette), Undated (Box 8)
  - IDA Artists Yr 2001-02 + 2002-03 (3.5" diskette), 2003 (Box 8)
  - The Signal: The Stanford Soundtrack vol. 7, 2008; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Gabriela Shiroma Photos, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - Come Sister Come ft. Leroy Mabrak, Genetic/Mabrak Music, 1997; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Karen Stroble "Unite" EPAMAD Video, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Invisible Scream 213.948.6123, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD)-R (Box 8)
  - Interstellar Highway Love Gone, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD)-R (Box 8)
  - Leilana Chan, TeAda, 2003; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD)-R (Box 8)
  - Andrea, Adam Matta, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - Of Cabbages and Kings, 2008; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - 10.4 Disc 1, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - 10.4 Disc 2, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - 10.4 Disc 3, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - 10.4 Disc 4, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - CBPA Fall 2002 Baraka/Harris Postcard, 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - Marcus Shelby Class, CBPA/Resident Dialogues, 28 Feb 2006; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Marcus Shelby, AAAS & CBPA, 3 Mar 2006; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Marcus Shelby IDA Noontime Series, 26 Jan 2006; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - The Wedding Project: A Resident Dialogues Presentation, 6 Jan 2006; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Octavia Butler 10/12/05, 12 Oct 2005; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Octavia Butler: Resident Dialogues 2005-06, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Harriet Tubman, Marcus Shelby, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - Marcus Shelby Jazz Orchestra 3/10/06, Marcus Shelby, 10 Mar 2006; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Watson, Johnson, Jackson: CD for BAQ 2002, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - BAQ Winter 2004, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - From Me To U, Juelz Santana, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - Works of Fethi Meghelli, Samir Meghelli, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - CBPA Reel Black, CBPA, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 8)
  - Singing Metal Bowls of Tibet, Benjamin Lobst, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 8)
  - Dreams: Polynesian Outreach 12/1/93 Tape #13, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD)-R (Box 8)